silveroakcasino.com 2017-06-11

# Silver Oak Casino Privacy Policy | Online Casino Games

Welcome to Silver Oak Casino, as a company we respect the privacy of our visitors and customers. Below you will find a pretty long legal document highlighting all of our terms when it comes to respecting your privacy. It's long and has a lot of legal terms in there, but what it really says is that we respect your privacy.

#### Introduction

Silver Oak Casino (the "Company" or "we") offers gambling services. In addition to offering its gambling services via the Internet (the "Internet Platform"), the Company may from time to time offer its services via alternative platforms such as (i) interactive television and (ii) mobile gaming platforms (each, an "Alternative Platform").

When you use the Company's gambling services, and whether such use is via the Internet Platform or an Alternative Platform, you shall be asked to provide personal information ("PI") to the Company.

The Company is committed to respecting your privacy and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws and we have therefore provided this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard your PI for the purpose of offering you gambling services. If you do not understand the Privacy Policy or how we handle or use the PI which you provide to us then you are invited to send in your questions to [help@silveroakcasino.com](mailto:help@silveroakcasino.com) and we will do our best to answer your questions in full as quickly as possible.

You should read this Privacy Policy in conjunction with the Silver Oak Casino Terms and Conditions.

#### Collecting Personal Information

We collect PI when you register and use our gambling services, make customer inquiries, register for information or other services from the Company, or when you respond to communications from us (such as questionnaires or surveys). The PI we will collect from you may include, for example, your name, email address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which the Company shall undertake.

#### How Your Personal Information is Processed ("Purposes")

The PI which you provide to us will be processed for one or more of the following Purposes: (i) to allow us to provide you with gambling services; (ii) to process any of your requests for information; (iii) to provide member support services to you; (iv) to market our services or products or those of other entities existing within the same group of companies in which the Company exists ("Silver Oak Casino"); (v) to notify you about updates to our software and/or services; and (vi) to support any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the PI.

#### To Whom Your Personal Information is Disclosed ("Recipients")

Your PI may, for the Purposes, be disclosed for processing to any of the following Recipients: (i) to any companies within Silver Oak Casino and their employees who have a need to know such information; (ii) to any third parties which provide services to the Company in order to allow or enable us to provide you with gambling services, including, by way of example, payment processors and data verifiers; (iii) to any third parties who provide Silver Oak Casino services in relation to the operation of all Silver Oak Casinos properties; (iv) to any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of Silver Oak Casino's business processes; and (v) to any potential purchasers or investors in any company within Silver Oak Casino. Any processing performed by any Recipients will, where required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights and obligating the Recipients to respect the PI and handle it in accordance with the relevant laws.

We ensure that your information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if required by law.

#### You Decide – Marketing?

Out of respect for your right to privacy we are happy to provide you with an easy means to decline receiving email offers from us. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers by sending a blank message with the word "Remove" in the subject area to [help@silveroakcasino.com](mailto:help@silveroakcasino.com).

The Casino reserves the right to publish your account username exclusively for marketing purposes, while keeping all your personal information completely confidential.

#### Your Rights in relation to your PI

You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your PI and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Where appropriate, you may have your PI rectified, amended or completed. Please email [help@silveroakcasino.com](mailto:help@silveroakcasino.com). We may levy a small charge to cover the cost of administration.

#### Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the entire PI under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your PI, are obliged to respect your privacy.

#### Cookies

We may send you a permanent cookie when you register with us. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can help us to recognize you when you next visit our website, note the advertisements you click on and the other sites you enter via a link from our website. This allows us to tailor the service we provide to your preferences. We may also use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept a cookie from us or from any other website. You can modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for instructions on how to do so correctly. However, for legitimate security reasons, we may refuse access to specific website content unless you accept the use of a cookie or similar device.

#### Protection of Minors

The services provided by the Company are not intended for or directed to minors or persons under the age of legal consent. Any person who provides us with PI represents to us that they are 21 years of age or over the age of legal consent in their jurisdiction. We reserve the right to access and verify any PI submitted by or collected from you. If we become aware that a minor has attempted to, or has submitted PI, we may not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from our records.

#### Retention

Your PI will not be stored for any longer period than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change, so please check it regularly. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. In the event the Purposes change, we will notify you as soon as possible and, where required seek your consent where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing.

If you have any enquiry about this Privacy Policy please write to [help@silveroakcasino.com](mailto:help@silveroakcasino.com).
